Julia Alonso Martínez

Project Manager



Valencia, Spain

Contact

Phone number: +31 630 22 18 22

Email: alonsomartinezjulia.1988@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/julia-alonso-martínez-13828b128

Summary

I work as a consultant in agile methodologies and project management at Getronics, from where I offer advice on agility implementations and project management to different teams, in addition to providing training in different work methodologies, planning, management by objectives, and OKR.

I have more than eight years of experience in Customer Service, which has allowed me to develop a strong sense of responsibility, organization, and empathy towards stakeholders.

Graduated in History from the University of Valencia, I obtained my Official Master's Degree in Project Management at the European University of Valencia. Additionally, I am certified by the Project Management Institute (PMI), Scrum.org, and Google.

In my free time I work as a volunteer at PMI Levante.

Professional Experience

 08/2023 – Present Consultant in Agile Methodologies Getronics

Advice and implementation of Agile Methodologies; applied Project management; training employees in project planning, management, quality and analysis (Waterfall and Agile); training employees in Planning and management by objectives, and OKR.

10/2022 – Present Project Manager

AVALNET

Project management; customer management; project requirement definition; project coordination; e-mail marketing; agile.

• 05/2022 – 10/2022 Project Manager

Freelance (self-employed)

Scrum master; project requirement definition; project coordination; requirements gathering; customer management.

07/2021 – 12/2021 Administrative Salesperson

Gana Energía

Customer management; incidences management and resolution; contract process monitoring; contract management; customer acquisition.

• 06/2017 – 07/2021 Specialist agent in telephone customer service

Atento España

Customer management; incidences resolution; appointment scheduling.

• 12/2015 – 05/2017 Agent in telephone customer service

Atento España

Customer management; incidences resolution.

Volunteering

• 06/2023 – Present **Project Management Institute**PMI Levante, Spain Chapter

Education

- 2022 2023 **Master's Degree, Project Management** Universidad Europea. Valencia, Spain
- 2013 2015 **Higher Education Training Cycle, Sign Language Interpretation** CIFP Misericordia. Valencia, Spain
- 2006 2011 Bachelor of Arts (BA), History Speciality in Ancient History Universitat de Valéncia. Valencia, Spain

Licenses and certifications

- Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)
 Project Management Institute. July 2022
- Professional Scrum Master I (PSM I)
 Scrum.org. July 2022
- OKR Certified Professional OKRCP CertiProf. Professional Knowledge. August 2022
- Google Digital Marketing & E-commerce Seven-course Professional Certificate

Google – Coursera. September 2022

- Agile with Atlassian Jira Atlassian. June 2022
- Google Project Management Six-course Professional Certificate
 Google Coursera. May 2022
- Digitization applied to the productive sector CEPYME. December 2021

Courses

- Practical English course What's Up! Academy
- OKR Goal Setting: The Complete Guide to OKRs Udemy
- Professional English for customer service Servef

• Library and Archives Technician – IVEP

Languages

- **German** A1 Level of the Common European Framework Reference for Languages (CEFR). German Center (Centro Alemán). July 2017
- Cambridge First Certificate in English (FCE) B2 level of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages (CEFR). 2016
- Intermediate Grade in Valencian Level C1 of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages. (CEFR). 2014